Finding Aid for the Daniel C. Prince Papers and S.T.A.R. Collection
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
- Negatives
  - Sleeves 181-191 (Box 75, File 19)
  - Sleeves 192-201 (Box 75, File 20)
  - Sleeves 202-210 (Box 75, File 21)
  - Sleeves 211-220 (Box 75, File 22)
  - Sleeves 221-230 (Box 75, File 23)
  - Sleeves 231-240 (Box 75, File 24)
  - Sleeves 241-250 (Box 75, File 25)
  - Sleeves 251-260 (Box 75, File 26)
  - Sleeves 261-271 (Box 75, File 27)
- Negatives
  - Sleeves 272-280 (Box 76, File 1)
  - Sleeves 281-291 (Box 76, File 2)
  - Sleeves 292-300 (Box 76, File 3)
  - Sleeves 301-310 (Box 76, File 4)
  - Sleeves 311-320 (Box 76, File 5)
  - Sleeves 321-330 (Box 76, File 6)
  - Sleeves 331-340 (Box 76, File 7)
  - Sleeves 341-351 (Box 76, File 8)
  - Sleeves 352-360 (Box 76, File 9)
  - Sleeves 361-370 (Box 76, File 10)
  - Sleeves 371-379 (Box 76, File 11)
  - Sleeves 380-390 (Box 76, File 12)
  - Sleeves 391-398 (Box 76, File 13)
  - Sleeves 399-410 (Box 76, File 14)
  - Sleeves 411-420 (Box 76, File 15)
  - Sleeves 421-430 (Box 76, File 16)
  - Sleeves 431-441 (Box 76, File 17)
  - Sleeves 442-451 (Box 76, File 18)
  - Sleeves 452-460 (Box 76, File 19)
  - Sleeves 461-469 (Box 76, File 20)
  - Sleeves 470-480 (Box 76, File 21)
  - Sleeves 481-490 (Box 76, File 22)
  - Sleeves 491-500 (Box 76, File 23)
  - Sleeves 501-510 (Box 76, File 24)
  - Sleeves 522-530 (Box 76, File 25)
  - Sleeves 531-544 (Box 76, File 27)